rezscore.com 2019-07-17

# RezScore

                                RezScoreSM Privacy Policy
Last updated: January 7, 2019
         Thank you for using RezScore.com. We are committed to protecting your privacy
and, for that reason, we have adopted this Privacy Policy to memorialize our data
collection and disclosure practices for our website and its related tools and services,
including any mobile application or website provided by us (collectively, the “Services”).
The Services are owned and operated by RezScore LLC, a Delaware limited liability
company (“RezScore,” “we,” “us” or “our”). This Privacy Policy applies to information
collected through the Services, as well as other information provided to us online or
offline by customers or users of our Services; however, it does not apply to information
collected from our employees, contractors or vendors. Specifically, this Privacy Policy
applies to persons using our site to submit their resumes and take advantage of special
offers and anyone else using or browsing our website or mobile application.
         At RezScore, we want to provide a safe and trustworthy user experience. We
understand that uploading your resume to our website may raise questions about your
privacy. Therefore, we hope you will take the time to read this Privacy Policy so that you
will understand how we protect your Personal Information.
1.       Consent
         By using the Services or our website, you consent to this Privacy Policy. If you
do not agree with this Privacy Policy, you may not use the Services or our website.
Information gathered through the Services may be transferred, used, and stored in the
United States and in foreign jurisdictions in which we, our agents, customers and other
users of the Services are located. If you access the Services, you consent to the transfer,
use and storage of your Personal Information (as defined below) in those jurisdictions.
The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be
as comprehensive as those in your country. You further agree that all transactions relating
to the Services or our website shall be deemed to have occurred in the United States.
2.       Collection of Personal Information
         We collect Personal Information in connection with our Services. When we use
the term “Personal Information” we are talking about information that can be used to
identify an individual and may include, but is not limited to, your name, address, phone
number, e-mail address, work history, education, employment status, industry affiliations
(e.g., the computer technology field) and areas of expertise, personal and professional
references, salary and pay history and requirements, and any profile or other information
you choose to submit through our Services. RezScore or its payment providers may also
collect credit, debit or other billing account information. As a general matter, whenever
you upload a resume to our website, we collect all of the information you choose to
include therein, including the categories of information listed above and any other piece

of Personal Information you include. You may always choose not to provide Personal
Information, but this may prevent you from receiving certain Services.
         If you choose to use our website’s social networking function to post information
to Facebook, Twitter, Tumblr, Reddit, StumbleUpon, or any another social networking or
information sharing site, we may collect your user ID and password information for that
site as necessary to make it easier for you to post to it.
         RezScore may also collect non-Personal Information (aggregate, non-individually
identifiable or demographic information). An example of non-Personal Information
would be system-related information such as IP addresses, use information, browser and
browser speed, bandwidth of your Internet connectivity, general location of your server
and the pages of our website that were viewed during a visit. We use this information for
internal purposes to help us diagnose problems, monitor traffic patterns and otherwise
continually improve our Services.
         Please note that the Services may provide links to third party sites, such as links to
the websites of the third-party organizations, businesses, and merchants. We are not
responsible for the privacy policies, practices or content of websites owned by others that
you may link to or that may be linked from the Services. Accordingly, we encourage you
to review the privacy policies and terms of service of those websites so that you
understand how those websites collect, use and share any Personal Information.
3.       Use of Personal Information
         RezScore uses the Personal Information in marketing products or services to you
through the RezScore.com platform; grading your resume; setting up your account;
improving online operations; processing transactions (for example, any credit, debit or
other billing account information collected from you will only be used to process
transactions requested by you); providing customer service; providing you with
newsletters, RSS feeds, and/or other communications or services which you have signed
up for or otherwise agreed to receive (for example, personalized resume review services
or information about our products and services); displaying content that is customized to
your interests or preferences (for example, we may target you with select job openings,
custom ads, messages and offers, basing our selections on information, such as industry
affiliations and employment history, and employment status, that you may choose to
provide to RezScore); if you choose to join our Leaderboard, a list of exemplary resumes,
posting your name, city and state, and industry affiliations/areas of expertise to the
Leaderboard; sending account- or transaction-related communications such as welcome
letters and transaction confirmations; performing research and analysis aimed at
improving our products, services and technologies; and managing our systems. We will
only use your Personal Information in the way we specified when it was collected
(including as described in this Privacy Policy).
4.       Disclosure of Personal Information

         We may disclose your Personal Information and non-Personal Information to
third parties, to the extent that we deem such disclosure necessary, in our sole discretion,
to deliver products or services that you have requested (including but not limited to
facilitating your receipt of personalized resume review services). In addition, we may
disclose Personal Information and non-Personal Information to companies, agents,
contractors, service providers or others engaged to perform functions on our behalf (such
as processing of payments, provision of data storage, hosting of our website, marketing of
our products and services, conducting audits, and performing web analytics).
         We may also disclose your Personal Information to third parties when we believe,
in good faith and in our sole discretion, that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a)
enforce or apply the terms and conditions of the Services, including investigation of
potential violations thereof, (b) comply with legal or regulatory requirements or an
enforceable governmental request, (c) protect the rights, property or safety of us, our
users or other third parties, (d) prevent a crime or protect national security, or (e) detect,
prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues. We may also disclose
non-Personal Information to our clients, business partners, merchants, advertisers,
investors, potential buyers and other third parties if we deem such disclosure, in our sole
discretion, to have sound business reasons or justifications. We do NOT sell, rent, share
or trade your Personal Information to third parties for their own marketing purposes
unless you have granted us permission to do so.
         Please note also that if you choose to use our social networking function to post
information to Facebook, Twitter, Tumblr, Reddit, StumbleUpon or any other social
networking or information sharing site, anyone who has access to your information
through that other site will be able to see your information.
         RezScore reserves the right to transfer information (including your Personal
Information) to a third party in the event of a sale, merger, or transfer of all or
substantially all of the assets of our company, or in the unlikely event of a bankruptcy,
liquidation or receivership of our business. Finally, RezScore may disclose aggregate
non-Personal Information to marketing partners, service providers, or other companies.
5.       Accessing and Updating Personal Information
         When you use our Services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with
access to your Personal Information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to
delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for
legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the
information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such
requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or
systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or
would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing
on backups), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case, where we
provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except
if doing so would require a disproportionate effort.

        Please e-mail us at privacy@rezscore.com with any questions, if you need
assistance accessing or changing your Personal Information, or if you would like to have
your Personal Information deleted. Please be aware that if you delete your Personal
Information, you may not be able to continue to use our website or the Services. Also,
even if you request that we delete your Personal Information, we may need to retain
certain information for a limited period of time to satisfy our legal, audit and/or dispute
resolution requirements.
6.      Cookies and Automatic Information Gathering Technologies
        Non-Personal Information (including aggregate, technical or demographic
information) can also be collected through the standard operation of our internet servers
and logs as well as other automatic data collection tools such as “cookies,” “beacons,”
“pixels” and other similar technologies. A “cookie” is a small text file that is recorded
either temporarily or persistently on your hard drive and that a website can use in order to
recognize visitors who revisit a website so as to facilitate their ongoing access to and use
of the website. “Beacons” and “pixels” are tiny electronic images designed to collect
web log information such as pages viewed or messages opened, and can be used to assist
us in determining how many users have visited certain pages or opened messages or
newsletters. Information we (or our service providers, such as our web analytics and e-
mail service providers) may collect through cookies, beacons and pixels includes your
browser type, language preference, operating system, referring website (if applicable), the
date and time of each user visit or request, the pages visited on our website, your IP
address and location, and any registries, message boards or other discussion forums
visited. We may also collect statistical information about the behavior of visitors to our
website on an aggregated, anonymous basis. Any information collected on our website
through the use of cookies, beacons or similar technologies will not be shared with third
parties for behavioral advertising or targeting purposes.
        Cookies can be prevented by activating the facility that is available in most web
browsers that enables the user to deny or accept cookies. Recognize, however, that
cookies may be necessary in order to provide certain features such as the customized
delivery of certain information. In no event do we use cookies, beacons, pixels or similar
technologies to collect Personal Information.
7.      International Users
        By visiting our website and by providing us with your Personal Information or
data, you acknowledge and agree that we may use the Personal Information or data
collected in the course of our relationship for the purposes identified in this Privacy
Policy or in our other communications with you, including the transmission of
information outside your resident jurisdiction. In addition, please understand that such
Personal Information and data may be stored on servers located in the United States. By
providing us with your Personal Information or data, you consent to the transfer of such
data to the United States. RezScore complies with all GDPR provisions.

8.       Children
         We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from users under 13 years of
age. We do not authorize users under 13 years of age to use the Services or our website.
If we learn that we have collected Personal Information from a child under the age of 13,
we will delete that data from our systems.
9.       Information Security
         We utilize reasonable information security measures to safeguard your Personal
Information. For example, we utilize Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology
when data is transmitted over the Internet, we have installed firewalls to help prevent
external access into our network, we store your resume information in encrypted
databases, and we use password protection and IP recognition for login. Unfortunately,
however, no data transmission over the Internet and no method of data storage can be
guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially
acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its security.
         We restrict access to Personal Information to RezScore employees, contractors,
service providers and agents who need to know that information in order to operate,
develop or improve our Services or website. These individuals are bound by
confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and
criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.
10.      Your California Privacy Rights
         A California resident who has provided personal information to a business with
whom he/she has established a business relationship for personal, family, or household
purposes (“California Customer”) is entitled to request information about whether the
business has disclosed Personal Information to any third parties for the third parties’
direct marketing purposes. In general, if the business has made such a disclosure of
Personal Information, upon receipt of a request by a California Customer, the business is
required to provide a list of all third parties to whom Personal Information was disclosed
in the preceding calendar year, as well as a list of the categories of Personal Information
that were disclosed.
         However, under the law, a business is not required to provide the above-described
lists if the business adopts and discloses to the public (in its privacy policy) a policy of
not disclosing customer’s Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing
purposes unless the customer first affirmatively agrees to the disclosure, as long as the
business maintains and discloses this policy. Rather, the business may comply with the
law by notifying the customer of his or her right to prevent disclosure of Personal
Information to third parties for direct marketing purposes and providing a cost free means
to exercise that right.

        We will not share Personal Information with third parties for their own direct
marketing purposes unless you affirmatively agree to such disclosure – typically by
opting in to receive information from a third party through our website.
        To prevent disclosure of your Personal Information for use in direct marketing by
a third party for its own purposes, do not opt in to or authorize such use when you
provide Personal Information on our website. Please note that whenever you choose to
share your Personal Information with a third party or allow your Personal Information to
be shared with a third party to communicate with you, your information will be subject to
the third party’s privacy policy. If you later decide that you do not want that third party
to use your information, you will need to contact the third party directly, as we have no
control over how third parties use information. You should always review the privacy
policy of any party that collects your information to determine how that entity will handle
your information.
        California Customers may request further information about our compliance with
California’s privacy law by e-mailing privacy@rezscore.com. Please note that we are
only required to respond to one request per customer each year, and we are not required
to respond to requests made by means other than through this e-mail address.
11.     Public Message Boards and Other Online Forums
        Please note that when you choose to post messages and/or profile content on
messages boards and other online forums that we may make available on our website,
such content is viewable by third parties and, in the case of public online forums and your
public profile, is publicly viewable. Accordingly, you should exercise discretion with
regard to what Personal Information you post on our website and should not post highly
confidential or sensitive information. RezScore is not responsible for how third parties
who view your Personal Information may use this information (such as to send you
unsolicited messages).
12.     Changes to this Policy
        RezScore may modify or update this Privacy Policy periodically with or without
prior notice by posting the updated policy on this page. You can always check the “Last
Updated” date at the top of this document to see when the Privacy Policy was last
changed. We may also post a notice of changes to this Privacy Policy on our website.
We encourage you to check this Privacy Policy from time to time. Your continued use of
our website and/or Services following the posting of an updated Privacy Policy
constitutes your consent to the contents of such policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO
FUTURE CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST STOP USING OUR
WEBSITE AND SERVICES AFTER THE EFFECTIVE DATE OF SUCH CHANGES.
12.     Questions
        To ask questions about our Privacy Policy or to lodge a complaint, contact us at:

RezScore LLC
Attn: Privacy Matters
792 Highland View Lane
Camano, WA 98282
Email: privacy@rezscore.com
